ineedpopcorn.com 2014-05-21

# Privacy Policy | cheezwheez.com

As always, the privacy, discretion and security of your personal information is cheezwheez.com’s (“cheezwheez.com”) top priority, and we want you to be aware of how we collect and handle information on our web site.

Cheezwheez.com does not collect personal information on this site. cheezwheez.com does not collect your credit card number or billing address, when you set up an online account. Our servers automatically collect statistical information about IP addresses, e-mail addresses and which browsers are used to visit our site. None of this information is associated with you as an individual. We use these statistics to monitor our site's performance and to make it easier for you to use. Children under eighteen years of age are not eligible to use our services. We request that children do not submit information to us or navigate our website.

We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission. 

Cheezwheez.com cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. 

We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by sending an e-mail to: info@cheezwheez.com and request that he or she be removed from our mailing list. Customers may also send a written opt-out request to the following address: 

Cheezwheez.com  
NETHERLANDS  

This website contains links to other web sites. Cheezwheez.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites linked to from our site. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the website, or your interaction with this website, you can contact us. 

Email: info@cheezwheez.com

Send mail to the following postal address:

Customer Service

Cheezwheez.com  
NETHERLANDS
